

Khoi Nguyen Le Minh

FRONTEND DEVELOPER REACTJS - 10 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE

- **** +84938925905
- mguyenkhoi2412@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I have over 10 years experience in web application development, especially in Front-end Web Development. I develop HTML / CSS / and javascript coding, making the site responsive and friendlier to smaller devices as well as improving performance. I like what I'm currently doing (Web Development!...). Challenging myself to learn new things and expanding my skillset - my driving force.

BASIC INFORMATION

06/01/1983 Birthday
Vietnamese Nationality
Married Marital Status
Male Gender

LANGUAGES



SKILLS

Front End, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS,

Css Responsive Design, HTML5, MVC, ASP.NET,

ReactJS, Ant Design, MongoDB, SQL

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY 09/2001 -

09/2001 - 08/2004

Information Technology

APTECH SCROOL 09/2001 - 08/2004

Expert programming

Higher diploma in software engineering

WORK HISTORY

.NET DEVELOPER

01/2022 - Current

Stepmedia Software Viet Nam (1 year 5 months)

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET CORE, C#, MSSQL, Azure
- Frontend is using REACTJS, SASS...
- Company product development Deloitte, maintain and develop new features according to customer, reports, improve performance for APIs, troubleshooting to perfect products...
- Test and write unit tests.
- Tracing error in application insights.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

01/2018 - 09/2020

CONEXUS VIET NAM (2 years 9 months)

- Conexus is a Global Edu Tech company in Norway. I am honor to be a member in the development team to build and develop an Enterprise Edu Tech project for Singapore market:
- Project domain: Unified Education and Training System
- users can use the system to organize learning courses, plan education and training programs for departments/organizations inside, host and manage e-learning sessions, review/assess/forecast learning courses and training programs.
- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5...
- My specialize is responsible develop UI with script, jquery, css responsive...

11/2012 - 01/2018

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Orient Software Development Corp. (5 years 3 months)

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5...
- My specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css responsive...
- Project domain: Unified Education and Training System
- users can use the system to organize learning courses, plan education and training programs for departments/organizations inside, host and manage e-learning sessions, review/assess/forecast learning courses and training programs.

DEVELOPER

06/2011 - 11/2012

VIEN NAM SOFTWARE (1 year 6 months)

- Programing projects websites for clients.
- Analysis, programming and development website application on the basic platform .NET 2.0, 3.5, 4.0... using ASP.NET, MVC, Entity Framework, Web services, html, jquery, css...

TECHNICAL SUPPORT

01/2008 - 01/2010

FPT TELECOM (2 years 1 month)

- Support clients about ADSL, LAN, WAN. Check client's connection on system, check information and all services assigned to clients.
- Support all problems that IT need to solve about Web server, mail server, FTP, IP static, NAT and troubleshoot IT's problems.

CERTIFICATIONS

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2004

University Of Technology

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2004

FPT Aptech